<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Radio4000 Blog</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Radio4000 Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Removing sign-up (then logins), with social providers Google and Facebook</title>
      <link>/posts/removing-social-provider-login-with-google-facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/removing-social-provider-login-with-google-facebook/</guid>
      <description>In an effort to free the project from dependencies, the creation of a new user (therefore a radio), will no longer be possible, using any external social providers. Also, in a close future we will enforce login with email/password for every users that are currently using social providers.
 Currently Facebook and Goole have been provided as a matter of convenience for user who might not wish to create for themeselves an account using an email/password pair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018 recap</title>
      <link>/posts/2018-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2018-recap/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s happened to Radio4000 in the year 2018? Let&amp;rsquo;s see.
You can search the tracks in a radio and listen to just that selection.
More on https://blog.radio4000.com/posts/search-tracks-listen-to-results
 Example: https://radio4000.com/lili-raid-over/tracks?search=%23beat.
 You can connect a Discogs release to your youtube tracks. When you do it, we try to add both genre, label and year to the description of the track. This works nicely with the seach feature. Speaking of Discogs, we also made an alpha version of a &amp;ldquo;Explorer for Discogs&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smarter Settings</title>
      <link>/posts/smarter-settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 13:51:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/smarter-settings/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve unified your Radio4000 settings. Now there&amp;rsquo;s a single location at radio4000.com/settings, where you can customize your radio, add it to the global Radio4000 map, make a backup or manage your account.
Before this update, settings were split between /auth/settings and /{channel-slug}/edit. Now, both will redirect to /settings.
If you are interested in the code changes, check the pull request #226.
And as always, please send feedback on https://radio4000.com/feedback. Enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Radio4000.com on mobile devices</title>
      <link>/posts/use-radio4000-on-mobile-android-firefox-and-lock-the-screen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/use-radio4000-on-mobile-android-firefox-and-lock-the-screen/</guid>
      <description>Since the beginning of the project Radio4000 has been thought, designed and coded to work well on every devices, operating systems and browsers.
One long time issue was using Radio4000 on mobile devices, because until now it was not possible to play a Radio4000 radio and lock the device&amp;rsquo;s screen.
This is now solved!
How to play Radio4000 with the mobile phone screen locked The solution is pretty simple, but will work only for Android and on Firefox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A list of online and offline radio channels</title>
      <link>/posts/radio-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 12:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/radio-list/</guid>
      <description>Most can be listened to online, on the broadcaster&amp;rsquo;s website or in some application. For the rest, you might have to connect to the AM/FM waves, turn on the radio in your car, also possibly change country.
Databases and applications  Transnational Radio Knowledge Platform - a great database of transnational radio stations, the one broadcasting on purpose over countries and borders. tunein - good user experience on this mobile application for listening to podcast and radios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to discover new music?</title>
      <link>/posts/how-to-discover-new-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 12:19:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/how-to-discover-new-music/</guid>
      <description>An extensive guide on how to discover new music. TBC.
How does new music appear? As silly as it sounds, some people create music and then decide to share it to the public. It can be shared on various supports, digital (a file, mp3, wav, aif, ogg, flac etc.), analog (tape, vinyl record), or mixed (CD, mixing digital and analog). The same music can be released on many supports. These suports have different properties, some make it easy to share the music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backup your Radio4000 radio data</title>
      <link>/posts/backup-your-radio4000-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 08:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/backup-your-radio4000-data/</guid>
      <description>While using Radio4000 each user are building a library of sounds. All the tunes added in your radio, its name, description, compose the data associated with your account on the application.
You own this data, all content you add on Radio4000.
Therefore you should have the possibility to always have this data stored where you would like. Radio4000 is simply a space online where you can store and edit it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search tracks, listen to results</title>
      <link>/posts/search-tracks-listen-to-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 15:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/search-tracks-listen-to-results/</guid>
      <description>Hello!
Today a new feature appears on the site, tracks search.
On top of now being able to search any radio tracks, and find the one you want to play, you can from today listen to a selection of tracks from a radio.
Fig 1. playing selection &amp;ldquo;#after&amp;rdquo; from Radio Tobha
That&amp;rsquo;s right, you can try it now, go to any radio (of course, yours too!), and explore the list of tracks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard shortcuts</title>
      <link>/posts/keyboard-shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 14:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/keyboard-shortcuts/</guid>
      <description>You enjoy discovering and sharing music on Radio4000, but you would like the experience to be done without the mouse, keyboard only?
We just implemented new Keyboard shortcuts to improve your time on the site. find the full up-to-date list on in the support center.
Fig 1: keyboard shortcut `g m`, &amp;ldquo;go to map&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Map for Radio4000</title>
      <link>/posts/map-for-radio4000/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 17:20:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/map-for-radio4000/</guid>
      <description>There is a new way to discover Radio4000 channels online, a map of the world.
As of today everyone can position their Radio4000 channel to one location in the world. So can you!
There are no restriction, nor any obligation. As always freedom first. You only decide if and where you would like your channel to appear on the map; where your body resides or your heart belongs, it is and will remain your choice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Embed a Radio4000 with an Iframe, on any website</title>
      <link>/posts/radio4000-player-embed-with-iframe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 23:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/radio4000-player-embed-with-iframe/</guid>
      <description>From today you can embed your Radio4000 onto any other webpage. Meet RADIO ARKOV.
How to use? You need to add to your site the following snippet of code. You will find the right code to be copied at the bottom of every Radio4000 radio page.
You can customize the values in pixels of `width` and `height` of this `iframe` HTML element to suit your design needs. If you look closer, you will see the part in the `src` property, ending with `?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protip: /play &amp; /play/random</title>
      <link>/posts/protip-quick-play-radio-and-play-random/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 09:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/protip-quick-play-radio-and-play-random/</guid>
      <description>Hello there,
just wanted to share with you two good tips to start listening to a radio as fast as possible.
Let&amp;rsquo;s take a radio, could be yours, could be anyone else&amp;rsquo;s, let&amp;rsquo;s say balls, radio4000.com/balls, hi balls!
When you want to play this radio on radio4000.com, you will probably type the address of radio4000 in your web browser, then visit the radio page before finally hitting the play button or a track on the chosen radio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>API for Radio4000.com</title>
      <link>/posts/api-for-radio4000com/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2017 15:47:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/api-for-radio4000com/</guid>
      <description>Yes, Radio4000 now officially has an API!
api: https://api.radio4000.com
documentation &amp;amp; code: https://github.com/internet4000/radio4000-api
This means you can now use the public data from Radio4000.com (such as the radio channels and their tracks) to create any softwares, hardwares, websites or applications.
What is an API?
An API (application programming interface) can take many aspects and is a term generally used in software development. In the current case we could summarize it as a set of tools and specifications defined (here by the Radio4000 team) to help developers apprehend and use data made available through the API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Radio4000 version 5</title>
      <link>/posts/radio4000-version-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 20:36:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/radio4000-version-5/</guid>
      <description>Good evening!
Tonight Radio4000 gets updated to a new major version (github#v.5.0.0). We&amp;rsquo;re happy to introduce some new features, and an effort to harmonize the overall experience across the software.
It is coming in with a new radio channel homepage and a new design now including the latest 10 tracks. A new subpage therefore appears under your radio, /tracks. This choice aims to help improve loading performances, and usability such as easing the experience of adding a new track to one&amp;rsquo;s radio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Radio4000 has a new player</title>
      <link>/posts/radio4000-has-a-new-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 21:47:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/radio4000-has-a-new-player/</guid>
      <description>Radio4000 has a new player. It has been deployed to all users since some days and will also allow anyone to embed and customize a player (or many) with any radio on their site.
It is written in javascript, html and css, the code is available on Github, radio4000-player package under npm.
 https://github.com/internet4000/radio4000-player https://www.npmjs.com/package/radio4000-player  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There is a new design for Radio4000</title>
      <link>/posts/there-is-a-new-design-for-radio4000-as-well-as-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 08:49:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/there-is-a-new-design-for-radio4000-as-well-as-a/</guid>
      <description>There is a new design for radio4000, as well as a new logo, and some new features:upgraded @usernames radio4000.com/your-usernamelogin with an email (use Email, Google, Facebook)link your Radio4000 to your Email, Google and Facebook, use any of the three (or the three) to login to your accountfilter radio channels be better serendipity; order them by last updated, age, or alphabetic ordersimplified navigation through the app and radio directorysend us a feedback or ask for help fastercontrol Radio4000 on your Android device when your screen is locked (works with Firefox browser)public API comming soon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s the small things…</title>
      <link>/posts/its-the-small-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2016 14:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/its-the-small-things/</guid>
      <description>A new update is out on Radio4000 &amp;mdash; it&amp;rsquo;s now faster to add a track to your radio. Whereas before you&amp;rsquo;d have to go to your radio and first then tap add track, now you can add directly from anywhere on Radio4000.
If you&amp;rsquo;re not already using the bookmarklet, you should try it out. After you&amp;rsquo;ve saved the bookmarklet it&amp;rsquo;s only two-taps to add a track while you&amp;rsquo;re browsing YouTube.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Radio4000 updates to version 3.3! What’s new?</title>
      <link>/posts/radio4000-updates-to-version-33-whats-new-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2015 09:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/radio4000-updates-to-version-33-whats-new-in/</guid>
      <description>Radio4000 updates to version 3.3! What’s new?In order to explore radios faster, we’ve added a “play ‘n shuffle” button on the radio channel cards. Try it, tap it as many times as you like, we think it makes listening much more fun. Your favorite radios are taking the place of the “most popular radios” section directly on the homepage.We’ve also started implementing a new design for radios, further innovations can be expected in the upcoming versions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use the Radio4000 bookmarklet to add tracks faster in my radio?</title>
      <link>/posts/how-to-use-the-radio4000-bookmarklet-to-add-tracks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 22:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/how-to-use-the-radio4000-bookmarklet-to-add-tracks/</guid>
      <description>How to use the Radio4000 bookmarklet to add tracks faster in my radio?Here is a solution that works for every one, on mac, pc, mobile, tablet or smartwatch (alright, possibly not that one), without having to install anything!Much simpler to explain it with gifs (above), but here is the text explanation:drag the bookmarklet to your browser’s favorite baropen a music you like on Youtube. Click the bookmarklet (you just added it in your browser’s favorite bar!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>v3.2.0</title>
      <link>/posts/v320/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2015 08:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/v320/</guid>
      <description>Time flies and so does our new copy on the website. It should be clearer what everything is now. Following along that, you will see that channel descriptions are now everywhere, on a channel detail or on its card &amp;mdash; tell there what your channel is about.
We also streamlined the header and player design while preparing for the Ember 2.0 update which should make everything leaner.
Oh, and we added a cheesy loading screen in fifty shades of languages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>v3.1.1</title>
      <link>/posts/v311/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2015 13:38:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/v311/</guid>
      <description>Today version 3.1.1 of Radio4000 is out!
When have included a bunch of new features, here is a small list:
 URL have changed! Find your channel directly at radio.com/yourRadio instead of radio4000.com/c/yourRadio. Easier to remember, more logic but remember to update the links pointing to your radio.  There is now a big Play button on every radio to listen to it straight when you open it. You can now see when a radio was last updated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>v3.1.0</title>
      <link>/posts/v310/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2015 16:44:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/v310/</guid>
      <description>Hi &amp;mdash; today we&amp;rsquo;ve been upgrading Radio4000 and it&amp;rsquo;s live!
 More images a bookmarklet to easily add tracks directly while you&amp;rsquo;re browsing YouTube. filtering and search is back on Discover everything is faster with the new Glimmer rendering engine from Ember.  All in all the best Radio4000 so far!
As usual, if you need help, have feedback or any other inquiries just use the way to contact us you prefer, please!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Site Update, May 2nd 2015</title>
      <link>/posts/site-update-may-2nd-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 07:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/site-update-may-2nd-2015/</guid>
      <description>What is new?
 support heavier images and .gif mobile design of the playback performances no more new radio prompt when you already had one  If you have a question or feedback you can send it to us via the comment of this post or on the Radio4000 Google group</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Older logs</title>
      <link>/posts/older-logs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 10:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/older-logs/</guid>
      <description>An internal timeline of things we pushed on Radio4000. Posted here so it doesn&amp;rsquo;t get lost in the internet.
[v3.0.0] 02.05.2015
Images, autosearch, bugs, design
[v2.0.0] 07.03.2015
Redesign, tabs, favorites and followers and tons of other improvements
[v1.2.0] 09.01.2015
Now you can shuffle
[v1.1.1] 01.01.2015
Fixes
[v1.1.0] 21.12.2014
On the world&amp;rsquo;s shortest day we managed to improve everything. We rewrote the playback functionality and performance is much better.
[v1.0.0] 25.10.2014</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>